<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seo on sig</title>
    <link>https://sigmonsays.github.io/tags/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seo on sig</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 10:38:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sigmonsays.github.io/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest invades google</title>
      <link>https://sigmonsays.github.io/pinterest-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 10:38:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sigmonsays.github.io/pinterest-sucks/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Pinterest is awful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has been growing for years. Here is the typical situation I think more people run into than you think. When you are looking for an image
on google image search and find what you are looking for by thumbnail, and click through just to be taken to pinterest.com. Once you land here,
you do not see any fragment of what you came for. Instead, you are confronted with a sign up page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has happened so many times to me and ive ranted to my friends about it before. However, It happened again recently and I also happened to read about it
later. So I am taking it upon myself to make this post, hopefully as a way to contribute to a small change: Pinterest not sucking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pinterest Sucks&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They require you to sign up for accounts to see any content yet manage to infect the SEO system of google search results. Both regular
results are affected but also image search.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even after logging into Pinterest, the image does not show. They are nothing more than click bait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They probably dont realize it but their decision is probably costing them accounts. I will never sign up for a pinterest account because of the terrible
user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can never find what im looking for. There is never a working link back to the original source.  Everything they do is garbage. They are the next generation
spammer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want ideas on coffee tables and want to look at a bunch of photos for ideas, they fit. However getting anything meaningful out of pinterest via search
is an exercise in futility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pinterest is a broken model&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its not just that Pinterest is spamming google searches, and that you have to search again once you get to Pinterest (assuming you have an account and are logged in).
Its also the fact that the majority of Pins are BROKEN- they dont lead back to the original source. (Whether because the pins are old, content has been moved, etc.)
So as opposed to a search engine like Google that continuously updates its index, the Pinterest model will only lead to more and more broken links as time goes by.
It is a broken model, and incredibly frustrating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;What can we do?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop using pinterest and help others to stop using pinterest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complain. Write blog posts, like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use an extension to block their results&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrome &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/personal-blocklist-by-goo/nolijncfnkgaikbjbdaogikpmpbdcdef?hl=en&#34;&gt;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/personal-blocklist-by-goo/nolijncfnkgaikbjbdaogikpmpbdcdef?hl=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firefox &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wildskyf/personal-blocklist&#34;&gt;https://github.com/wildskyf/personal-blocklist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;references:e809b07ecd33fccb59a427cc6c8c434a&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[1] &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/google/comments/85atho/pinterest_needs_to_be_removed_from_google_imo/&#34;&gt;reddit thread mar18 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>